Guide to the Arlen Specter Senatorial Papers, Group 4. Office Administration Files, 1962-2010 TJU.2010.01.04
ULS Archives & Special Collections
- Administrative Assistant Files, 1962-2010; I.
  - Larry Kosten, 1981-2002; 18.
    - Hadassah, The Women's Zionist Organization of America, 2002 (Box 605, Folder 23)
    - Homeland defense/Anti-Terrorism Act hearings, 2001 (Box 605, Folder 24)
    - Homeland Security establishment, 2002 (Box 605, Folder 25-26)
    - Johnson v. Reno, 2000 (Box 605, Folder 27)
    - Peter Lee, Report, 2002 (Box 605, Folder 28)
    - Wen Ho Lee, Report, 2000 (Box 605, Folder 29)
    - Military tribunals, Quirin precedent, 2002 (Box 606, Folder 1)
    - Miscellaneous, 2002 (Box 606, Folder 2)
    - Mentor, National Mentoring Partnership, 2002 (Box 606, Folder 3)
    - The New Marshall Plan, 2002 (Box 606, Folder 4)
    - Oversight, 2001 (Box 606, Folder 5)
    - Pennsylvania State Corrections Officers Association, undated (Box 606, Folder 6)
    - Physicians for Social Responsibility, 2002 (Box 606, Folder 7)
    - Pickering district court judge letter, undated (Box 606, Folder 8)
    - Polygraph, 2001 (Box 606, Folder 9)
    - Secret Service agents lawsuit, 2002 (Box 606, Folder 10)
    - Brooks Smith Court of Appeals nomination, 2001 (Box 606, Folder 11)
    - Specter action in Israel, 1981-1996 (Box 606, Folder 12)
    - Specter floor statement on Israel and Palestine, undated (Box 606, Folder 13)
    - Specter floor statement on Middle East, 1997 (Box 606, Folder 14)
    - USA Patriot Act, FISA Process, 2002 (Box 606, Folder 15)
    - Zionist Organization of America, 2002 (Box 606, Folder 16)
  - Jonathan Levin, 1981-1983; 19.
    Jonathan Levin served as staff assistant, 1981-1983.
    - Debt collection, 1981 (Box 606, Folder 17-18)
    - Federal Deposit Insurance Act, 1981 (Box 606, Folder 19)
    - Immigration, 1982-1983 (Box 606, Folder 20-26)
  - Bill Loughrey, 1962-2003; 20.
    Bill Loughrey served as: staff assistant, 1981-1982; chief legislative assistant, 1983; and staff director, 1984.
    - Agriculture, 1981-1982 (Box 607, Folder 1)
    - Agriculture, Budget, 1982 (Box 607, Folder 2)
    - Agriculture, Coal slurry pipeline, undated (Box 607, Folder 3)
    - Agriculture, Farm labor contracts, 1979-1981 (Box 607, Folder 4)
    - Agriculture, Harrisburg meeting, 1981 (Box 607, Folder 5)
    - Agriculture, Pennsylvania flooding project, 1981-1982 (Box 607, Folder 6)
    - Agriculture, Rural Electrification Administration, 1980-1983 (Box 607, Folder 7-8)
    - Bills, HR. 1338-3635, 1983 (Box 607, Folder 9)
    - Bills, HR. 4201-5573, 1984 (Box 607, Folder 10)
    - Bills, S. 19-101, 1983 (Box 607, Folder 11)
    - Bills, S. 118-406, 1983 (Box 607, Folder 12)
    - Bills, S. 408-501, 1983 (Box 607, Folder 13)
    - Bills, S. 503-605, 1983 (Box 607, Folder 14)
    - Bills, S. 633-819, 1983 (Box 607, Folder 15)
    - Bills, S. 829-830, 1983 (Box 608, Folder 1)
    - Bills, S. 851-1029, 1983 (Box 608, Folder 2)
    - Bills, S. 1034-2036, 1983 (Box 608, Folder 3)
    - Bills, S. 1182-1526, 1983 (Box 608, Folder 4)
    - Bills, S. 1535-1660, 1983 (Box 608, Folder 5)
    - Bills, S. 1680-1762, 1983-1984 (Box 608, Folder 6)
    - Bills, S. 1763-1980, 1983 (Box 608, Folder 7)
    - Bills, S. 1983-2505, 1983-1984 (Box 608, Folder 8)
    - Bills, S. 2550-3001, 1984 (Box 608, Folder 9)
    - Bills, Cosponsored bills, 1983 (Box 608, Folder 10)
    - Bills, Credit Deregulation and Availability Act, 1981 (Box 608, Folder 11)
    - Bills, Credit Deregulation and Availability Act, Hearing statements, 1981 (Box 608, Folder 12)
    - Budget, 1981-1982 (Box 608, Folder 13)
    - Budget, 1982 (Box 608, Folder 14)
    - Budget, 1982 (Box 609, Folder 1-2)
    - Budget, Analysis, 1982 (Box 609, Folder 3)
    - Budget, Banking, 1981 (Box 609, Folder 4)
    - Budget, Government Accounting Office (GAO) commentary, 1981 (Box 609, Folder 5)
    - Budget, Interior appropriations, 1984 (Box 609, Folder 6)
    - Budget, Program for economic recovery, 1981 (Box 609, Folder 7-8)
    - Budget, Reconciliation, S. 1377, 1982 (Box 609, Folder 9-10)
    - Budget, Revising second budget resolution, 1981 (Box 609, Folder 11-12)
    - Budget, Summary and special tables, 1982 (Box 609, Folder 13)
    - Campaign finance, 1990-1992 (Box 609, Folder 14-16)
    - Campaign finance, 1990-1992 (Box 610, Folder 1)
    - Campaign finance hearing, 1990 (Box 610, Folder 2)
    - Chertoff allegations, 2001-2003 (Box 610, Folder 3)
    - Chronological files, February-April 1981 (Box 610, Folder 4)
    - Chronological files, May-June 1981 (Box 610, Folder 5)
    - Chronological files, August-September 1981 (Box 610, Folder 6)
    - Chronological files, October-November 1981 (Box 610, Folder 7)
    - Chronological files, December 1981 (Box 610, Folder 8-9)
    - Chronological files, 1981 (Box 610, Folder 10)
    - Chronological files, January-April 1983 (Box 610, Folder 11)
    - Chronological files, May 1983 (Box 610, Folder 12)
    - Chronological files, June-August 1983 (Box 610, Folder 13)
    - Chronological files, September-October 1983 (Box 610, Folder 14)
    - Chronological files, November 1983 (Box 610, Folder 15)
    - Chronological files, November-December 1983 (Box 611, Folder 1)
    - Chronological files, January 1984 (Box 611, Folder 2)
    - Chronological files, February 1984 (Box 611, Folder 3)
    - Chronological files, March 1984 (Box 611, Folder 4)
    - Chronological files, April 1984 (Box 611, Folder 5)
    - Chronological files, September 1984 (Box 611, Folder 6)
    - Chronological files, November 1984 (Box 611, Folder 7)
    - Chronological files, December 1984 (Box 611, Folder 8)
    - Chronological files, January 1985 (Box 611, Folder 9)
    - Chronological files, February 1985 (Box 611, Folder 10)
    - D.C. subcommittee, 1981-1983 (Box 611, Folder 11)
    - Energy, 1982 (Box 611, Folder 12-13)
    - Energy, Correspondence, 1983 (Box 611, Folder 14)
    - Energy, Drake Chemical, 1982 (Box 611, Folder 15)
    - Energy, Drake Chemical, Newsclips, 1962-1983 (Box 611, Folder 16)
    - Energy, Hydropower, 1981-1983 (Box 611, Folder 17)
    - Energy, Hydropower bill, 1981-1982 (Box 611, Folder 18)
    - Energy, Hydropower hearings, 1982 (Box 611, Folder 19)
    - Energy, Jobs, 1982-1983 (Box 611, Folder 20)
    - Energy, Joliett generating station, 1983 (Box 612, Folder 1)
    - Energy, Legislation, 1981-1983 (Box 612, Folder 2)
    - Energy, Mining, 1981-1983 (Box 612, Folder 3)
    - Energy, Mining Reclamation Bill, 1983 (Box 612, Folder 4)
    - Energy, Mining Reclamation Reserve Act, 1981 (Box 612, Folder 5-8)
    - Energy, Oil, 1981-1983 (Box 612, Folder 9-10)
    - Energy, Pennsylvania Rural Electric Association, 1984 (Box 612, Folder 11)
    - Energy, Rural Abandoned Mine Program, 1981-1982 (Box 612, Folder 12)
    - Energy, SRC-1 Synthetic Fuels Program, undated (Box 612, Folder 13)
    - Erie office, 1982 (Box 612, Folder 14)
    - Holy Land Foundation, 2001-2003 (Box 612, Folder 15-16)
    - Internal agencies, 1979-1982 (Box 613, Folder 1)
    - Internal agencies, Commerce/Maritime/Environmental Proetction Agency (EPA), 1981 (Box 613, Folder 2)
    - Iraq, 1990-1991 (Box 613, Folder 3)
    - Israel supercomputer, 1990 (Box 613, Folder 4)
    - Jewish affairs, 1978-1992 (Box 613, Folder 5-6)
    - Kurds, 1991 (Box 613, Folder 7)
    - Labor, Health and Human Services (LHHS), 1982 (Box 613, Folder 8)
    - Martino and McLaughlin, 1998 (Box 613, Folder 9)
    - Mediation board, 1981 (Box 613, Folder 10)
    - Miscellaneous office, 1981-1983 (Box 613, Folder 11-14)
    - Miscellaneous topics, 1982-2004 (Box 613, Folder 15-16)
    - Oklahoma City bombing, 2002-2003 (Box 613, Folder 17)
    - Oklahoma City bombing, 2002-2003 (Box 614, Folder 1-2)
    - PATRIOT Act, 2003 (Box 614, Folder 3)
    - Pennsylvania projects, 1981 (Box 614, Folder 4)
    - Phone calls, 1984 (Box 614, Folder 5)
    - Recession, 1982 (Box 614, Folder 6)
    - Recession, Constituent mail, 1982 (Box 614, Folder 7)
    - Reelection, 1982 (Box 614, Folder 8)
    - Securities legislation, 1995-1997 (Box 614, Folder 9-11)
    - Trade, 1982 (Box 614, Folder 12)
    - Voter outreach, 1992 (Box 614, Folder 13)
  - Tom Madine, 1987-1989; 21.
    Tom Madine served as: executive assistant, 1982, 1989-1993; staff assistant, 1983-1985; grant coordinator, 1986-1987; and senior staff assistant, 1988.
    - Grant notices, 1987 (Box 614, Folder 14-16)
    - Grant notices, 1987 (Box 615, Folder 1-8)
    - Grant notices, 1988-1989 (Box 615, Folder 9-12)
    - Grant notices, 1988-1989 (Box 616, Folder 1-2)
    - Memos, 1987 (Box 616, Folder 3)
    - Memos, 1988 (Box 616, Folder 4)
    - Trips, 1987 (Box 616, Folder 5)
    - Trips, 1988 (Box 616, Folder 6-7)
  - Neal Manne, 1981-1988; 22.
    Neal Manne served as administrative assistant, 1987-1988.
    - Alcohol advertising, 1985 (Box 616, Folder 8)
    - Antitrust, 1985 (Box 616, Folder 9)
    - Antitrust, Administrative proposals, 1986 (Box 616, Folder 10-11)
    - Antitrust, Beer bill, 1985-1986 (Box 616, Folder 12)
    - Antitrust, National Football League (NFL) television contract, 1985-1987 (Box 616, Folder 13)
    - Antitrust, Newspapers, 1985 (Box 616, Folder 14)
    - Antitrust, Retail price fixing, 1985 (Box 616, Folder 15-16)
    - Appropriations supplement, 1985 (Box 616, Folder 17)
    - Archaeological objects, 1985 (Box 616, Folder 18)
    - Atlanta murders, 1985 (Box 616, Folder 19)
    - Ballot and election fraud, 1987 (Box 617, Folder 1)
    - Robert Bork nomination, 1985-1987 (Box 617, Folder 2-4)
    - Brock, Business and labor leaders, 1986 (Box 617, Folder 5)
    - Bureau of Justice reports, 1983-1985 (Box 617, Folder 6)
    - Campaign finance bill, 1983-1987 (Box 617, Folder 7)
    - CIA reform, 1985 (Box 617, Folder 8)
    - Child abuse, 1985 (Box 617, Folder 9)
    - Child pornography, 1985 (Box 617, Folder 10)
    - Civil Rights Commission, 1986 (Box 617, Folder 11)
    - Communications, 1984-1986 (Box 617, Folder 12)
    - Copyright, Audio taping, 1984-1986 (Box 617, Folder 13)
    - Copyright, Cable, 1981-1985 (Box 617, Folder 14-16)
    - Corporate Take Over Act, 1984-1985 (Box 617, Folder 17-18)
    - Corporate Tax Act, 1984-1985 (Box 617, Folder 19)
    - Delaware River Basin Commission, 1985 (Box 617, Folder 20)
    - Discrimination, Congress, 1985 (Box 617, Folder 21)
    - Federal Prison Industries, 1986 (Box 617, Folder 22)
    - Former flight engineers relief, 1982-1985 (Box 617, Folder 23)
    - Home/mental illness, 1987 (Box 618, Folder 1)
    - Juvenile offenders, 1984-1985 (Box 618, Folder 2)
    - Kennedy nomination, 1987-1988 (Box 618, Folder 3)
    - Legal aid, 1985 (Box 618, Folder 4)
    - Legislation schedules, 1983-1985 (Box 618, Folder 5)
    - Letters, January 1987 (Box 618, Folder 6)
    - Letters, February 1987 (Box 618, Folder 7)
    - Letters, March 1987 (Box 618, Folder 8)
    - Letters, April 1987 (Box 618, Folder 9)
    - Letters, May 1987 (Box 618, Folder 10)
    - Letters, June 1987 (Box 618, Folder 11)
    - Letters, July 1987 (Box 618, Folder 12)
    - Letters, August 1987 (Box 618, Folder 13)
    - Letters, September 1987 (Box 618, Folder 14)
    - Letters, October 1987 (Box 618, Folder 15)
    - Letters, November 1987 (Box 618, Folder 16)
    - Letters, December 1987 (Box 618, Folder 17)
    - Letters, January 1988 (Box 618, Folder 18)
    - Letters, February 1988 (Box 618, Folder 19)
    - Letters, March 1988 (Box 618, Folder 20)
    - Letters, April 1988 (Box 618, Folder 21)
    - Letters, May 1988 (Box 618, Folder 22)
    - Letters for signature, Constituents, 1987-1988 (Box 618, Folder 23)
    - Letters for signature, Legislative, 1987-1988 (Box 618, Folder 24)
    - Letters for signature, Office and staff, 1987-1988 (Box 618, Folder 25)
    - LHT Industries, 1985-1986 (Box 618, Folder 26)
    - Mallory case, 1987 (Box 618, Folder 27)
    - McKean County, 1985 (Box 618, Folder 28)
    - Edwin Meese, Attorney General nomination, 1984-1985 (Box 618, Folder 29)
    - Memos, July 1986 (Box 618, Folder 30)
    - Memos, August 1986 (Box 618, Folder 31)
    - Memos, January 1987 (Box 618, Folder 32)
    - Memos, February 1987 (Box 618, Folder 33)
    - Memos, March 1987 (Box 618, Folder 34)
    - Memos, April 1987 (Box 618, Folder 35)
    - Memos, May 1987 (Box 618, Folder 36)
    - Memos, June 1987 (Box 618, Folder 37)
    - Memos, July 1987 (Box 618, Folder 38)
    - Memos, August 1987 (Box 618, Folder 39)
    - Memos, September 1987 (Box 618, Folder 40)
    - Memos, October 1987 (Box 618, Folder 41)
    - Memos, November 1987 (Box 618, Folder 42)
    - Memos, December 1987 (Box 618, Folder 43)
    - Memos, January 1988 (Box 618, Folder 44)
    - Memos, February 1988 (Box 618, Folder 45)
    - Memos, March 1988 (Box 618, Folder 46)
    - Memos, April 1988 (Box 618, Folder 47)
    - Memos, May 1988 (Box 618, Folder 48)
    - Josef Mengele, 1985 (Box 618, Folder 49)
    - Missing children, 1985 (Box 618, Folder 50-51)
    - Nuclear waste, 1985 (Box 619, Folder 1)
    - Patlex patent, 1985-1986 (Box 619, Folder 2)
    - Pennsylvania political action committees (PACs), 1985 (Box 619, Folder 3)
    - Pennsylvania Republican city chairmen, 1985 (Box 619, Folder 4)
    - Philadelphia Manpower Project, 1987-1988 (Box 619, Folder 5)
    - Polygraph, 1986 (Box 619, Folder 6)
    - Pornography Victims Protection Act, 1985 (Box 619, Folder 7)
    - Prisons, 1985-1986 (Box 619, Folder 8)
    - Privatizing Corrections, 1985 (Box 619, Folder 9-10)
    - Product liability, 1985 (Box 619, Folder 11)
    - Rape, Webb hearing, 1985 (Box 619, Folder 12-13)
    - Rules, 1986 (Box 619, Folder 14)
    - Rules Enabling Act, 1985 (Box 619, Folder 15)
    - School prayer, 1985 (Box 619, Folder 16)
    - Securities and Exchange Commission (SEC), All holdings, 1984-1985 (Box 619, Folder 17)
    - SEC, Appropriations, 1985 (Box 619, Folder 18)
    - SEC, Tender office, 1985 (Box 619, Folder 19)
    - Sentencing, Child victims, 1984-1985 (Box 619, Folder 20)
    - South Africa, 1986 (Box 619, Folder 21)
    - Superfund, 1985 (Box 619, Folder 22)
    - Supreme Court Resolution., 1983-1987 (Box 619, Folder 23)
    - Synthetic drugs, 1985 (Box 619, Folder 24)
    - Tax plan, 1985 (Box 619, Folder 25)
    - Techworld, 1985-1986 (Box 619, Folder 26)
    - Teenage suicide, 1982-1985 (Box 619, Folder 27)
    - Telephone/MCI, 1986 (Box 619, Folder 28)
    - Telephone rate, 1985 (Box 619, Folder 29)
    - Texas corruption case, 1985 (Box 619, Folder 30)
    - Torture, 1986-1987 (Box 619, Folder 31)
    - Trade, Unfair foreign competition, 1985 (Box 619, Folder 32)
    - Trade bill, 1985 (Box 619, Folder 33)
    - Trade bill, 1985 (Box 620, Folder 1-3)
    - Trade bill, Hearing, 1985 (Box 620, Folder 4)
    - Trans World Airlines (TWA), 1986 (Box 620, Folder 5)
    - Vigilantism, 1985 (Box 620, Folder 6)
    - War Powers Act, 1985-1987 (Box 620, Folder 7)
    - Welfare reform, 1986 (Box 620, Folder 8)
    - Youth-Run Courts, 1984-1985 (Box 620, Folder 9)
  - Patrick Meehan, 1984-1994; 23.
    Patrick Meehan served as executive director, Philadelphia office, 1991-1994.
    - Abortion, Newsclips, 1992 (Box 620, Folder 10)
    - Gregg Adelman, Ongoing projects, 1994 (Box 620, Folder 11)
    - Agricultural Stabilization and Conservation Service (ASCS)/U.S. Department of Agriculture (USDA) consolidation in Clearfield, 1993 (Box 620, Folder 12)
    - Alcohol advertising, 1993-1994 (Box 620, Folder 13)
    - American Airlines, 1993 (Box 620, Folder 14)
    - Appalachian Trail, 1984 (Box 620, Folder 15)
    - Arctic drilling, 1988 (Box 620, Folder 16)
    - Arms sales, United Nations (UN) funding, 1993-1994 (Box 620, Folder 17)
    - Army Reserve aviation restructuring, 1993-1994 (Box 620, Folder 18)
    - AT&T, Newsclips, 1991 (Box 620, Folder 19)
    - Avenue of the Arts, Philadelphia, 1993 (Box 620, Folder 20)
    - Balanced Budget Amendment, 1993-1994 (Box 620, Folder 21)
    - Banks, Savings and loans, Newsclips, 1990-1991 (Box 620, Folder 22)
    - British Thermal Unit (BTU) tax, 1993 (Box 620, Folder 23)
    - Bucks County contamination, 1993 (Box 620, Folder 24)
    - Budget process, 1989 (Box 620, Folder 25)
    - President George H.W. Bush, Newsclips, 1991-1992 (Box 620, Folder 26)
    - Business, Newsclips, 1991 (Box 620, Folder 27)
    - Buy America, 1993 (Box 620, Folder 28)
    - Campaign industry news, 1990 (Box 620, Folder 29)
    - Career criminal cases, 1987-1988 (Box 620, Folder 30)
    - CBS Philadelphia baseball tickets, 1993 (Box 620, Folder 31)
    - Census, Newsclips, 1990-1991 (Box 620, Folder 32)
    - CIA, Newsclips, 1991 (Box 620, Folder 33)
    - Chester County Exton bypass funding, 1991 (Box 620, Folder 34)
    - Chester County wage decision, 1992-1993 (Box 620, Folder 35)
    - Civil rights bill, Newsclips, 1990 (Box 620, Folder 36)
    - Clean Air Plan, 1989 (Box 620, Folder 37)
    - Clean air, Press, undated (Box 620, Folder 38)
    - Clean Water Act, 1994 (Box 620, Folder 39)
    - Constituents, Alliance for the Mentally Ill of Pennsylvania, 1994 (Box 620, Folder 40)
    - Constituents, American Zionist Federation, 1986 (Box 620, Folder 41)
    - Constituents, Ashland Hospital, 1993 (Box 620, Folder 42)
    - Constituents, Black Barristers, 1992 (Box 620, Folder 43)
    - Constituents, Breast Health Institute, 1992 (Box 620, Folder 44)
    - Constituents, Chester County Republican Committee, 1993-1994 (Box 620, Folder 45)
    - Constituents, Chronic Fatigue Immune Dysfunction Syndrome Support Network, 1992 (Box 620, Folder 46)
    - Constituents, CAS, 1993-1994 (Box 620, Folder 47)
    - Constituents, Clarion County Republican Committee, 1993 (Box 620, Folder 48)
    - Constituents, Conservative PAC RSVP, 1994 (Box 620, Folder 49)
    - Constituents, Core States, Philadelphia Bank, 1994 (Box 620, Folder 50)
    - Constituents, Counseling or Referral Assistance services, 1991 (Box 620, Folder 51)
    - Constituents, Defense attorneys, 1992 (Box 620, Folder 52)
    - Constituents, Delaware County Republican Party, 1994 (Box 620, Folder 53)
    - Constituents, Evangelical Manor, 1994 (Box 620, Folder 54)
    - Constituents, FOUNDATIONS, 1988-1989 (Box 620, Folder 55)
    - Constituents, Friends of Labor, 1994 (Box 620, Folder 56)
    - Constituents, Gaudenzia, 1993 (Box 620, Folder 57)
    - Constituents, General Communications, Inc., 1994 (Box 620, Folder 58)
    - Constituents, Heinz Family Foundation, 1993 (Box 620, Folder 59)
    - Constituents, The Heritage Foundation, 1993 (Box 620, Folder 60)
    - Constituents, Hope Industries, 1993 (Box 620, Folder 61)
    - Constituents, Independence Blue Cross, 1994 (Box 620, Folder 62)
    - Constituents, Jewish organizations, 1987-1989 (Box 620, Folder 63)
    - Constituents, Juvenile Diabetes Foundation, 1994 (Box 620, Folder 64)
    - Constituents, Korean and American Friendship Society, 1993 (Box 621, Folder 1)
    - Constituents, Krieble Institute, 1993 (Box 621, Folder 2)
    - Constituents, LaMott, 1994 (Box 621, Folder 3)
    - Constituents, Lower Bucks County Chamber of Commerce, 1993 (Box 621, Folder 4)
    - Constituents, Lower Gwynnedd Township Police Department, 1993 (Box 621, Folder 5)
    - Constituents, Mainstream Access, undated (Box 621, Folder 6)
    - Constituents, Marine Corps reunion, 1994 (Box 621, Folder 7)
    - Constituents, Medgraphix International, 1993 (Box 621, Folder 8)
    - Constituents, Minority Business Enterprise Council, 1991-1994 (Box 621, Folder 9)
    - Constituents, Monroe County Republican Council, 1993-1994 (Box 621, Folder 10)
    - Constituents, National Association of Retired Federal Employees, 1992-1994 (Box 621, Folder 11)
    - Constituents, National Committee on U.S.-China Relations, 1994 (Box 621, Folder 12)
    - Constituents, National Institute of Neurological Disorders and Strokes, 1993 (Box 621, Folder 13)
    - Constituents, National Refrigerants, 1993 (Box 621, Folder 14)
    - Constituents, Pennsylvania peace groups, 1985 (Box 621, Folder 15)
    - Constituents, Pennsylvania public interest group, undated (Box 621, Folder 16)
    - Constituents, Pennsylvania rabbis, 1992 (Box 621, Folder 17)
    - Constituents, Pennsylvania State Association of County Commissioners, 1989-1990 (Box 621, Folder 18)
    - Constituents, Pennsylvania superintendents, undated (Box 621, Folder 19)
    - Constituents, Philadelphia area business leaders, 1986-1989 (Box 621, Folder 20)
    - Constituents, Philadelphia College of Textiles and Science, 1994 (Box 621, Folder 21)
    - Constituents, Philadelphia Electric Company, 1993 (Box 621, Folder 22)
    - Constituents, Philadelphia Food Corporation, 1994 (Box 621, Folder 23)
    - Constituents, Philadelphia Lager Beer Brewers Association, 1993 (Box 621, Folder 24)
    - Constituents, Philadelphia Marine Trade Association, 1990-1993 (Box 621, Folder 25)
    - Constituents, Philadelphia Maritime Museum, 1994 (Box 621, Folder 26)
    - Constituents, Philadelphia Republican Policy Committee, 1993-1996 (Box 621, Folder 27)
    - Constituents, Planned Parenthood of Southeastern Pennsylvania, 1994 (Box 621, Folder 28)
    - Constituents, Port of Philadelphia leaders, 1992 (Box 621, Folder 29)
    - Constituents, Preservation of the Faith Theological Seminary, 1993 (Box 621, Folder 30)
    - Constituents, Redevelopment Authority of the City of Erie, 1993 (Box 621, Folder 31)
    - Constituents, Republican Committee of Allegheny County, 1993 (Box 621, Folder 32)
    - Constituents, Republican Committee of Lower Merion and Narberth, 1993 (Box 621, Folder 33)
    - Constituents, Roosevelt Paper Company, 1993 (Box 621, Folder 34)
    - Constituents, Saint-Goban Corporation, 1993 (Box 621, Folder 35)
    - Constituents, Seneca Group, 1994 (Box 621, Folder 36)
    - Constituents, SNI Company, 1994 (Box 621, Folder 37)
    - Constituents, South Philadelphians United, 1990-1991 (Box 621, Folder 38)
    - Constituents, Southeastern Pennsylvania Transportation Coalition, 1994 (Box 621, Folder 39)
    - Constituents, Sterling Winthrop, 1992-1994 (Box 621, Folder 40)
    - Constituents, Technology Council of Greater Philadelphia, 1994 (Box 621, Folder 41)
    - Constituents, Terri Lynne Lokoff Foundation, 1992 (Box 621, Folder 42)
    - Constituents, Town Development, 1994 (Box 621, Folder 43)
    - Constituents, United Way of Southeastern Pennsylvania, 1990-1992 (Box 621, Folder 44)
    - Constituents, University of Pennsylvania Cancer Center, 1993 (Box 621, Folder 45)
    - Constituents, Valley Forge Flag Company, 1993 (Box 621, Folder 46)
    - Constituents, Wistar Institute, 1993 (Box 621, Folder 47)
    - Constituents, Women leaders, 1986-1992 (Box 621, Folder 48)
    - Constituents, Women Organized against Rape, 1990-1992 (Box 621, Folder 49)
    - Constituents, Women's Community Revitalization Project, 1991-1992 (Box 621, Folder 50)
    - Crime bill, 1991-1994 (Box 621, Folder 51)
    - D&H Rail Line liquidation, 1990 (Box 621, Folder 52)
    - Death penalty, 1989 (Box 621, Folder 53)
    - Defense Clothing factory conversion, 1993 (Box 621, Folder 54)
    - Delaware and Lehigh Navigation Canal Heritage Corridor, 1991-1992 (Box 621, Folder 55)
    - Delaware County EPA, Radiation sites, 1993 (Box 621, Folder 56)
    - Delaware River Port Authority, 1990-1992 (Box 621, Folder 57)
    - Department of the Interior, 1990 (Box 621, Folder 58)
    - Department of Justice, 1991 (Box 621, Folder 59)
    - Desert Storm help phone numbers, 191 (Box 621, Folder 60)
    - Digital telephony issue, 1994 (Box 621, Folder 61)
    - Domestic violence, 1994 (Box 621, Folder 62)
    - Drugs, Newsclips, 1990-1994 (Box 621, Folder 63)
    - Duke University Diet and Fitness Center, 1993 (Box 621, Folder 64)
    - Earth Week, 1992 (Box 621, Folder 65)
    - Education, Newsclips, 1990-1991 (Box 621, Folder 66)
    - Elderly, 1992-1993 (Box 621, Folder 67)